Welcome students, you all are welcome to my
YouTube channel IB Jobs Date, so we will
meet again today with a new vacancy. Today
your vacancy has come out, that is
from ICICI Bank New Requirement 2030. The
total
number of posts in this is
3560.
Its post name is PO, your vacancy has come out for color and honor posts.
What is the online date of when will the forms be filled?
So your forms have started filling from January 2,
2023. Your forms have started and
when is the last rank, when will they be filled,
your forms will be filled till February 28, 2023. If there is an
application in this, then nothing will be
kept in it. General candidates, OBC, UG, SC
and PG, no candidate has to deposit any fee. The
form will be online from zero.
What is the further limitation asked for? The age should
be 18 years. What is the
qualification kept in this? One should be 10th
pass, toll pass and
graduation.
How will it be? So there will be an interview for the selection process
and  There will be documentation,
how much salary will you get, if it is from 26000 to
64000 per month, you will be
given salary in this, if we
talk about location, then the answer will be from India,
you are from any state, from any
district, from any area, you
can apply in this form,
how did you like the information given by me,
do tell me in the comment section, like and
share the video, if you are new to my channel
then definitely subscribe to the channel,
Jai Hind, Jai Bharat